I had hip surgery last January a little
bit about me had hip surgery
some kind of weird coupon I got
you gotta use them mom says you gotta
use the coupon well you think cool to
have an hip surgery of my age as I had a
cane for three months and I'm a single
male adult any single males in here all
right be a little bit more enthusiastic
man yeah
[Applause]
any single ladies in here - you all
right I think you're sitting next to
your boyfriend actually so that was
weird all right that's it all right
that's cool whole row ladies didn't say
anything that's cool all right shoulda
brought my cane should've brought my
cane dude if you have a cane single dude
in the back that doesn't say yeah very
well if you have a cane dude it's
amazing man let me know just walk up
they would just walk up all time just oh
oh why what why well I just had hip
surgery and every woman says the same
thing you know you ladies say oh my
grandma just had hip surgery
but yeah i was playing bingo with her
last night she's a very lovely lady
she's very nice I did not like going to
the hospital by myself I look like this
I'd have to go into orthopaedics part of
the hospital what you ever done that
you're gonna orthopedics parts just oh I
like old men did not like me old men
every time I walked in would just mean
mugged me like I'm cougar hunting on
their turf that's there was one man bill
it was like why are you always in here I
sell coffins I guess some of you got
that some of you it's gonna be a long 40
minutes for me
[Music]
I learned one very important thing you
have a hip surgery at my age okay you
have a dream chase it you have one life
to live maximize it right okay two of
you that's cool all right never had dead
silence on that before
Bravo you tell you did it good for you
guys no don't cheer that's not a
compliment
you guys already weird I've been up here
for minutes you're already weird leave
your dream you what we like to live
everybody in here yeah yeah doing it
already doing it next next joke
fake dad is that isn't your missus
wasn't your missus right there there you
go
how long you been together 20 years my
end of marriage right everybody wants to
get married yeah that's a good number 20
years what's key to a successful
marriage man meat foot wine your and
you're good at it
[Music]
I think the best answer I ever got when
I asked that question was like what so
how do you what's the key to a
successful marriage the guy goes never
go to sleep angry and I was like oh okay
and then I tried to move on and then he
blurted it out it goes and I am in slept
in seven years if you enjoyed that you
can watch more of me you watch my entire
special for actually 99 cents it's
pretty it's pretty good deal or you can
just watch more clips and click here and
click on one of these things it gets
both hurry up and click the camera guys
having a baby right now he's got to get
to the hospital you need to hurry up and
click click on something anything just
once